

Andrei Alb

DATE OF BIRTH: 03/04/1991

CONTACT

Nationality: Romanian

Gender: Male

73, Dimitrie Cantemir Blvd.040231 Bucharest, Romania

albandrei01@gmail.com

(+40) 0757724307

main.emdev.ro

https://github.com/ WhiteAndrew91

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/andrei-alb-351a9b12a/

ABOUT ME

I am a self-taught developer. My Front End coding journey started at the beginning of 2020 when I decided to follow a 2 - month coding bootcamp. So far, I feel really interested in working with APIs and generating animations. In the future, I would like to learn more about HTML's canvas feature and how could I use JavaScript in order to create applications based on Virtual and Augmented Reality. Furthermore, I would like to learn a Node.js framework in order to understand the concepts of Back End architecture and being able to tackle more ambitious projects with an expanded level of expertise.

WORK EXPERIENCE

05/2019 - 11/2019

Real Estate Market Analyst

Yardi

- Analyzes the information flow regarding various office and industrial buildings
- Localizes and collects information about real estate properties all across the Unites States of America
- Studies the documents that represent ownership titles and identifies information regarding the parties involved in financial transactions such as sales or mortgages
- Identifies and studies the documents representing construction or portfolio loans, ground lease situations or any other valuable information regarding all the properties listed on Yardi Matrix platform
- Updates and maintains the quality of information inserted in the company's platform database

Cluj-Napoca, Romania

10/2017 - 04/2018

HR Support Assistant with French

Societe Generale European Business Services

- Management of the requests received by phone or email on HR and IT topics as well as other software applications available on the Group's Intranet Portal
- Recording all the demands and decide whether they can be solved by the Tier 1 team or if they need to be transferred towards the Tier 2 or Tier 3 level teams
- Guiding customers toward the use of self-service options available on a specific platform while offering support at the same time, if needed

- Reporting toward the second level team any type of incident affecting the proper functioning of the used application
- Seeking assistance from the Contact Center Team Manager or Coordinator in order to close the complex demands;

Bucharest, Romania

10/2016 - 06/2017

Kitchen Line Assistant

Hard Rock Caffe

Reykjavik, Iceland

11/2015 - 06/2016

Bartender

La Pas Caffe

Alba Iulia, Romania

10/2015 - 11/2015

Sociology Research Assistant

"Little Prince" Association

Alba Iulia, Romania

09/2013 - 02/2014

Book Retailer

Antic Ex-Libris

Bucharest, Romania

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

03/2020 - 04/2020 - Bucharest, Romania

Junior Front End Developer / Javascript

Coders Lab

The course included 240 hours of study structured as follows:

Module 1. Introduction to programming

Module 2. JavaScript

Module 3. Responsive Web Design

Module 4. ECMAScript6

Module 5. JavaScript ReactJS

Module 6. Workshops

Field(s) of study

Information and Communication Technologies

https://www.coderslab.ro/

09/2018 - 07/2019 - Cluj-Napoca, Romania

MSc in Complex Data Analysis

Babes-Bolyiai University

- Structured and visual basic language for applications (SQL)
- Databases exploration and visualization
- Statistical programming in Python
- Methodology of social research
- Spatial Analysis of social and economic processes in GIS

EQF level 7

2013 - 2015 - Bucharest, Romania

MA Degree in Sociology

National School of Political Studies and Public Administration of Bucharest

EQF level 7

2010 - 2013 - Cluj-Napoca, Romania

Bachelor in Psychology

Babes-Bolyai University

EQF level 6

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Romanian

English

Listening C2	Reading C2	Spoken production C1	Spoken interaction C1	Writing B2
French				
Listening B2	Reading B2	Spoken production B2	Spoken interaction B2	Writing B2
Spanish				
Listening A2	Reading A2	Spoken production A2	Spoken interaction A2	Writing A2

DIGITAL SKILLS

Coding

Web-Development / Responsive Web Design / React.js / HTML 5 / CSS 3 / WebStorm / JavaScript / jQuerry / SCSS/SASS / Python - basic / Git Version Control / Visual Studio/Visual Studio Code

General IT skills

UNIX Shell script / WIndowsmacOS operating systems / G-Suite Google (Google Classroom Google Meet Google Docs Google Forms etc) / IT Hardware Software / Basic Networking

Microsoft Office Suite

Microsoft Office(Microsoft Excel Microsoft Word Microsoft Powerpoint Microsoft Access) / Outlook

PUBLICATIONS

Publications

- Informal Trade in Tineretului Neighbourhood in *Urban Spaces in Action : Community activation in Bucharest's socialist neighborhoods,* Bucharest, 2015. (http://www.studiobasar.ro/?p=6423)
- Bucharest Neighborhood: **A socio-anthropological research**, Bucharest, 2015.(http://beta.asociatia-komunitas.ro/pdf/Cartier-de-Bucuresti.pdf)
- Dissertation thesis: Consuming practices, marginalization and harm reduction policies related to injectable drug use: an anthropological view in press.

PROJECTS

Projects

- June 2015 : *Timpuri Noi in Action -* social researcher (http://www.studiobasar.ro)
- June 2015 : Bucharest 2021 : European Capital of Culture report editor
- September 2014 : **Urban Education workshops** (http://asociatia-komunitas.ro)
- June-September2014 : *Urban Spaces in Action -*social researcher (http://asociatia-komunitas.ro/spatii-urbane-in-actiune)